Guide to the Three Arrows Cooperative Society, Inc. Records TAM.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: 2011 Addendum, undated
  - Membership Meetings, 1986-2011 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2008-2010 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2011 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Series V: Photographs, 1940s-2006
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition I, [2006] (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition II, [2006] (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Captions), [2006] (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Oversize), [2006] (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Photographs), [2006] (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Anniversary, 70th: Exhibition (Print and Graphic Materials), [2006] (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - General Photographs, 1940s-1950s (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - General Photographs, circa 1960s (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - General Photographs, 1964-1967 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - General Photographs, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - General Photographs, 1970s (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - General Photographs, 1990s (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - General Photographs, 2000s (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - General Photographs I, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - General Photographs II, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - General Photographs (Oversize), 1998, undated (Flat-file-folder 9)
  - Landscape Photographs, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Watercolors, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 31, Box 15)
  - Justus and Jenny Ebert, 1889-1945 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Series VI: Maps and Plans, 1937-1981
  - New Community Bulding Plan, 1952 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Norman Thomas Hall Plan, 1952 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Property Layout and Names, 1939-1940 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Putnam Valley Plan, Rochdale Road, 1948 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Social Hall Plan, 1952 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Three Arrows and Vicinity, 1968 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Three Arrows Property Map [Original and 2 copies], 1963 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Three Arrows Sites and Names, 1966 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Three Arrows Structures and Site Locations, undated (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Three Arrows Survey and Plan [2 sheets], 1937 (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - United States Department of the Interior Geological Survey: Mohegan Lake Quadrangle, 1981 (Flat-file-folder 3)
- Series VII: 2014 Addendum, 1941-2014
  Scope and Content Note
  This series contains materials that was donated to the library in 2014, with materials dating from the early 1940s up until 2014. The materials include budget documentation; board of directors and membership meeting minutes reporting on Three Arrows committees; by-laws; plays, songs, and poetry possibly performed at the cooperative; programs of performances; correspondence between members regarding the governance of Three Arrows; and their newsletter, The Voice of the Hill.
  - Flash drive, 2010-2014 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Budget Information, 2011-2014 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Meeting minutes, 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Plays, Poems, and other Writings related to Three Arrows, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence related to Governance of Three Arrows, 2012-2013 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Labor Day Shows, 1941-2013 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Camp Play Photograph with Bobb Vladeck and Betsy Bosworth, circa 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Songs, 1940s-1960s (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - The Voice of the Hill, 1956-1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Series VIII: Archived Websites, August 2017-ongoing; 2 websites in 2 archived websites.
  The Three Arrows Cooperative Society, Inc. is the successor organization to the Barger Street Cooperative Society, chartered in 1937. Early members purchased 125 acres of farmland in Putnam Valley, NY and formed a cooperative summer colony which eventually grew to include 75 individual units. The colony, sometimes known as Camp Three Arrows, is modeled on socialist and communitarian values and offers residents a wide range of cultural, educational and leisure activities. The website contains information on property listings, news articles about the the co-op, planning meeting listings, calendar of events, activities offered, area attractions, governance, publications, and information related to the "Save the Lake" initiative to keep toxic algae growth from Barger Pond.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of threearrowsco-op.net and threearrowsco-op.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
- Series XII. 2022 Addenda, 1984-2022; 175.1 Megabytes in 252 documents
  Scope and Contents
  This accretion consists of correspondence, ephemera, notices, and planning materials for anniversary celebrations, as well as 252 pdfs documenting the Three Arrows Cooperative Society's administrative operations, finances, and anniversary celebrations. Materials also include copies of the group's newsletters.
  - Administrative Records, 2010-2021; cuid36297 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_250_ER_4)
  - Anniversary, 2022; cuid36298 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_250_ER_5)
  - Finances, 2009-2022; cuid36299 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_250_ER_6)
  - Minutes, 2011-2021; cuid36300 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_250_ER_7)
  - Trees and Lake, 2014-2019; cuid36301 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_250_ER_8)
  - Voice of the Hill, 2014-2019; cuid36302 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_250_ER_9)
  - 60th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Programs and Event Flyers, 2006-2021 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Member -- Amy Vladek Heinrich, 2018-2021 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Notices, 2017-2018 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Nursery Restoration, 2018 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Story Hour, 2017-2018 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Susan Robbins Berger, 1984-2011 (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
  - Archives Committee, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Lake and Trees, 2020 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Literary Supplement, 2021 (Box 18, Folder 11)